http://www.calnative.com/privacy.html

This privacy policy applies to The
California Native International Adventures and its websites Calnative.com, CopperCanyonTours.com, and TheCaliforniaNative.com. This privacy policy informs users of how we collect, store and manage data about our users that is gathered on our websites.
INFORMATION OF A NON-PERSONAL NATURE
Our websites actively log and record information of a non-personal nature such a referral websites, visits, length of sessions, domains and more. We aggregate and use this non-personal data to improve our website experience for our guests.
HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
You are not required to submit personal information to use our websites. Our websites will not automatically record any information about users which is readily personally identifiable. However, you may submit your personal information to us on our websites, through the telephone, and by email. Any information that you voluntarily submit may be used by us to provide you with information such as notices of new products and services..
We may also share your information with legal authorities in response to subpoenas, court orders and other legal processes, and to exercise our legal rights as may be required by the law.
INFORMATION GIVEN TO SUPPLIERS BY US
In order for us to provide your travel and tour services we may be required by our suppliers to provide your personal information to them. In such cases we strive to provide only the necessary information. These suppliers include tour operators, cruise lines and railroads that provide travel services for our clients.
FINANCIAL AND CREDIT CARD INFORMATION
We do not share your credit card information or any of your financial data with our partners or suppliers, nor do we retain any of this information after it is processed to our account.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
The California Native reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Statement at any time and for any reason. If there are material changes to this statement or in how we will use your personal information, we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. Please check back periodically to learn of any changes in ways in which we may use this data.
AGREEMENT OF USE
By using our websites, you are indicating that you have read and accepted the information practices in our Privacy Policy.
DATA SECURITY
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
THIRD PARTY ADVERTISEMENTS AND USE OF COOKIES
The California Native uses third party vendors and these providers show our ads across different sites on the internet. Our third party vendors include Google, Yahoo, MSN and others. Our ads appear on networks across the internet from these and other providers. Some of these third party vendors including Google use cookies to deliver you ads based on any previous visits you may have made to our website. You may opt-out of the use of Google cookies by visiting the Google ads opt-out page.
OPT-OUT POLICY
To opt out of The California Native mailings, simply click the link at the bottom of our emails labeled "Unsubscribe." You can
also email us at travel@calnative.com, enter your email address, and title the email "Unsubscribe."
To update, correct or remove any personal information stored in our database, or if you have further questions regarding this policy and its use please contact us.
For more information, contact us at:
Information by Mail.
Phone us at:
E-mail us at:
The California Native
6701 W. 87th Place, Los Angeles CA 90045
CST 2027100-40
